Two is in the case, and by Pastor 1st turn to Terrain Church Raven.
Thank you very much for being here tonight!
I have six to nine for the consent agenda. If there are no questions or concerns, only of those items that indicate motion two approved
The consent agenda as recommended?
Mr Prouf
On second it roll call please
Hi
We're a vice-corner
All right
Work at
Aye
Item 10 is the Minden chapter 24 utility section 24 day 49
Up division 2 with regard to establishing a minimum kilowatt adjustment
The strategy you got to join next week
This is what this says a copification of the rate that we're already doing
And was in our ordinances before
and all are great tables have been done for last 10 years, whatever
It didn't really get put taken out
Essentially
This is a minimum kilowatt adjustment
And this on our commercial rates and our industrial rigs
What it's for, those particular services are very expensive
For the time
Transmores your money
$5000 to 50 thousand dollars in most
Of course they're labor-free
So what happens if there were designs or loads of design
To recover expenses from that over a period 5 years
But if the load drops off
We have no way to recover that totally expensive
And thats what a minimum KW demand is
Our recovery's through our demand charge
So therefore, we'll just down lower at certain point
I said
The minimum will be $7 per kw based on some of their summer rate
That has been an nutshell
What this says and going over with Ben
And this is the codeification
What we're actually doing right now
So that's it
A nutshell I'll be happy to answer any questions
Any questions for data and concerns
Do you have a motion?
To approve item 10 as recommended
I'm like every second
Second
We will call please
Foraster
Work at Westives Lewis
Hi, Chul
Item 11 is related to the same item
Says reestablishing minimum KW adjustment
Into a firm subcity weight level
Correct
That was this of course
To reaffirm in the minimum adjustment
Thats The same thing we just talked about
But our sub-sensivary rate
Those are huge that don't understand what it Is
That is the rate that was put into place before I even got here
And it Was a very good action on The Carter City
and there reason wasn't
It's an enticement to pick up new industrial load
Industrial loads
Instead of going To like REC in fact
i.e., On-the other side
In 5th during this time
This rain came became the B
We lost
From rac loss below
Then city Gotit
Now its work
Because JNTL
But the low is work
Very good loads of we have
And We continue keeping these rates
All those stuff
Anyway,
I never actually put that in our ordinances
The rate
The line which has there
To allow us to do it
It's Never been written
In what
What a really hits
That ss with this
Is an writing and you can codify
Within Our Ordnance
So it does not change
You want to do table comes out or something
Okay
Any questions you're concerned on
I am 11
Do we have a most-year proof
Posture
Second
Roll call please
Or get
Weston
Forester
Loose high
Sholes
Thanks David
In New Business Anyone
And he truste community announcements
Iron 14 is the German
We are almost two german issue
On my way
To have second
World Health
Show
Forester
Bye
Loose high
Work it